https://www.adoptionmiracles.org/privacy-policy

Call Now:
Birth Mothers
Hoping to Adopt?
Birth Mothers
Hoping to Adopt?
Privacy Policy
THE USE OF THIS WEBSITE, AND THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR OUR PROVIDING INFORMATION HEREON, IS GOVERNED BY THE TERMS SET FORTH BELOW. BY USING THIS WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ THE LIMITATIONS AND DISCLAIMERS CONTAINED SET FORTH BELOW AND THAT YOU ACCEPT AND WILL BE BOUND BY THE TERMS HEREOF.
Your privacy is important to us. This policy outlines our commitment to your privacy regarding the information you provide to us, and also states the limitations placed on your use of this website.
We may collect two types of information from you when you visit our website. The first type is personally identifiable information, or that which is identifiable to you as an individual. The second type is non-personally identifiable information, or that which is not identifiable to you as an individual.
Personally Identifiable Information
Adoption miracle collects no personal information identifying you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide that information voluntarily. We receive and store personally identifiable information that you voluntarily enter on our website. You can choose not to provide this information, but you might not be able to take advantage of some of the website’s features as a result of such decision. To the extent you do choose to share personally identifiable information with us, please know that we do not sell or rent any such information that we receive over our website. In general, we will not share this data with anyone outside of adoption miracle, or those hired by adoption miracle, to perform work on its behalf. However, we might share such data in unusual circumstances, such as for security reasons, pursuant to a subpoena or court order, or in response to a law enforcement request. Further, in the unlikely event of a merger or combination with another organization, its lists may be transferred to a successor organization.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
We also collect such non-personally identifiable information as the type of web browser you use, your domain name and links you may have used to locate our website, the machine originating the request, and the time of the request. This data may be logged for access statistics and security purposes. Use of this website constitutes consent to such monitoring.
If you have questions regarding these policies please contact Renee Halsnik Adoption Miracle at (813) 654-6911.
Let us help.
We understand that emotions can be running high when facing an unplanned pregnancy and often times, you want to talk to someone outside of normal business hours. For this reason, we are available to any birthparents, 24 hours a day, 7 days a week. If we cannot answer immediately due to confidentiality reasons, please leave a voicemail and we will call you back!
Name
Email
Phone #
Approximate Due Date
Address
Message
Send
